

■ tonyjly@gmail.com

tonyly.com

**425-343-3711** 

**♥** Kirkland, WA

# **EDUCATION**

### **SUMMARY**

2016 University of New

England College of Pharmacy
PharmD

University of

Washington BS Microbiology Recent graduate from pharmacy school in Maine with PharmD degree. Possesses seven years of pharmacy experience in a retail setting in Washington state. Excellent interpersonal skills matched with a history of establishing positive relationships with patients, pharmacy colleagues, and fellow medical professionals. Seeking a pharmacist position that will utilize extensive pharmacy education, clinical training, and provide the opportunity to practice high-quality, patient-centered, and interprofessionally collaborative health care.

# **SKILLS**

2011

PHARMACY INFORMATICS: R, Python, Linux

**ELECTRONIC HEALTH RECORD SOFTWARE:** Epic, Meditech, GE Centricity

# **EMPLOYMENT**

### TARGET PHARMACY

Pharmacist Intern

Redmond, WA Apr 2013 to Aug 2014

- Answered clinical drug information questions from patients and pharmacy staff
- Assisted in verifying accurate antibiotic dosing and dose intervals
- Processed medication requests from patients
- Interpreted prescriptions for patients via electronic patient profiles to minimize risk of DDIs and to identify possible contraindications
- Interprofessional collaboration with prescribers via telephone to ensure accurate and appropriate therapy to patients
- Prepared oral antibiotic suspensions for patients
- Provided patient education on proper medication usage and possible side effects

### UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON, DEPT OF PHARMACEUTICS

Research Technician II (Lin Lab)

Seattle, WA Jun 2010 to Aug 2012

- Primary research in identifying endogenous biomarkers for cytochrome P450 metabolism
- Extracted compounds of interest from human biological specimen via liquid-liquid extractions
- Conducted biological sample analysis via High-Performance Liquid Chromatography-Tandem Mass Spectrometry (HPLC/MS-MS)
- Compiled metabolomics database using Quadrupole-Time of Flight (Q-TOF) instrumentation

#### TARGET PHARMACY

Pharmacy Technician

Redmond, WA Aug 2007 to Apr 2013

- Processed medication requests from patients
- Prepared medication refills for final check by pharmacist
- Performed inventory and placed daily orders
- Organized outdated and overstocked medications for return to salvage

### **PROJECTS**

#### VANCOMYCIN THERAPEUTIC DOSING AND MONITORING PROGRAM

Conducted retrospective outcomes evaluation on pharmacist-driven vancomycin dosing and monitoring protocols in inpatient and acute care settings. Spearheaded data analysis enhancement with pharmacy informatics integration to automate data collection.

## **PROFESSIONAL LICENSURE**

#### WA DOH PHARMACIST LICENSE (PH60686691) · Pending

- NAPLEX successfully completed
- MPJE pending December 2016